麦克斯  谢谢你愿融入圣诞气氛
Max, thanks for agreeing to get in the spirit
还做节日小蛋糕
and do holiday cupcakes.
比起你去年喝到酩酊大醉
So much better than last year when you go so drunk
把《圣诞十二日》
you turned the 12 days of Christmas
变成了"圣诞戒酒十二步"
into the 12 steps of Christmas.
是啊  这次我终于放弃啦
Yeah, well, I finally gave in.
圣诞节就像疱疹
Christmas is like herpes.
无论你怎么防范
No matter what you do,
它每年都会卷土重来一次
it's gonna flare up once a year.
你做了西语的"圣诞快乐"小蛋糕
Oh, you made Feliz Navidad cupcake.
我"灰常"以你为荣
I'm muy proud of you.
我觉得等"明天款爷来了"
And I think we're going to make muy mucho moolah
我们会赚"灰常多钱钱"
when Manuel comes manana.
你是我认识的人中
You're the only person I know
唯一个越说西语越像死白人的人
who seems whiter speaking Spanish.
西语版"圣诞快乐"给说西语的朋友们
Feliz Navidad for our Spanish speaking friends.
给跟我一样背景的孩子  圣诞你认错爹"乐"
And for kids raised like me,  Feliz "He's-not-your-dad."
还有普通人版的"欢乐满人间"
And then, "Joy To The World" for the normals,
以及嬉皮士版的"大麻满人间"
and for the hipsters, "Joint To The World."
给小孩的"雪人霜霜仔"[圣诞儿歌]
For the kids, "Frosty The Snowman."
以及给你的"雪特没人爱"
And for you, "Frosty With No Man."
冰霜杰克难道就有垂幸你的咪咪头吗
Well, I didn't see Jack Frost nipping at your nips either.
这个  这是我的最爱
Oh, here, this one's my favorite,
圣诞老人"来了"...
"Santa Claus Is Coming"--
麦克斯  求别说
Max, stop right there.
没了  就这样  圣诞老人来了
No, that was it. He's coming.
厄尔  拜托找零
Earl, change please.
"厄尔  求你改改吧[找零]"
"Earl, change please."
我两任前妻都对我说过这句话
A phrase I heard from both my ex-wives.
你这里的圣诞卡
Wow, you have more Christmas cards
比"刀锋跑者"杀人案的借口还多啊
than Oscar Pistorius had excuses.
我能说啥  我想把善心散播出去啊
What can I say, Max? I spread a lot of goodwill.
我的衣服也都是"善心"二手店买的
It's also where I get all of my shirts.
给  祝节日愉快
Here you go. Have a nice holiday.
我两个孩子可喜欢每年这个时候了
My two kids love this time of year.
明年圣诞节  就变三个孩子了
And next Christmas, there will be three.
还是个男孩
It's a boy.
我远在阿富汗驻扎的老公听了可开心了
My husband was so happy when I called him in Afghanistan.
节日期间的人们都太好搞定
Man, this time of year people are easier
比穿着抹胸的肥妞还好"搞"
than a fat girl in a tube top.
太好了  我们可以用这笔钱
Oh, great. We can use this money
再去多订一点小蛋糕T恤
to order more of our cupcake T-shirts.
不行  这笔钱是要拿来给大家买圣诞礼物的
No, we are using that to buy people Christmas gifts.
我本来还很期待送给人一些"得到"后
I was really looking forward to giving someone something
不需要去打青霉素针的"东西"[梅毒]呢
that wouldn't require the follow-up penicillin shot.
我们需要更多T恤  这衣服真得很畅销
We need more shirts. These are really selling.
第四桌的那个男的说这衣服
The guy at table four said it's the perfect gift
最适合拿来送给纯约炮  不谈情的女人了
for a girl you're not in love with, just strictly banging.
他买了三件呢
He bought three.
我碰巧知道
I happen to know for a fact
店里的大家都有东西要送我们
that everyone here's getting us stuff.
阿憨今天上班带了个小包裹[小屌]来
Han came in with a small package today
然后手上还拿着一袋礼物
and also he was carrying a gift bag.
我们会凑出钱来买礼物的
We'll find some money for the gifts.
大家肯定觉得只会收到小东西
People aren't expecting anything big.
节日快乐
Happy holidays.
大家觉得会拿到的"小东西"来了
People just got the nothing big they were expecting.
请集合一下  我有份很特别的礼物
Gather, please. I have a very special gift
要送给餐厅各位员工
for all my diner employees.
健康保险吗
Health insurance?
你闹呢  是圣诞节  又不是傻蛋节
Come on, it's Christmastime, not crazy time.
是独一无二的丝网印刷艺术品
It's art. It's a one of a kind silk screen.
我自己动手做的
I did it by hand.
你一直以来不都是"自己动手做"吗
I figured that's how you always have to do it.
阿憨  是餐厅  这太棒了
Han, it's the diner. This is amazing.
打开门  我在门后放了
Open the door. I put something behind it
会让我想起你们的代表物件
that reminds me of each of you.
我的是苏菲
Mine has Sophie.
我的是萨克斯风
Mine has a saxophone.
我的是小蛋糕
Mine has a cupcake.
我的是电锯
Mine has a chainsaw.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
节日购物妙方
Holiday shopping tip:
在星巴克杯里装伏特加
Fill a Starbucks cup with vodka.
购物侍应两相宜哦
Also good for waitressing.
苏菲  你去圣诞血拼了吗
Sophie, were you Christmas shopping?
肯定是啦
Oh, you know I was!
接线板
Power strips!
挺好啊  你买了有电涌保护器的接线板
Oh good. You got surge protectors.
哇  那是你的公寓里
Wow, that's the first time protection's
首次使用"保护措施"吧
ever been used in your apartment.
我的圣诞装饰需要7万5千瓦电力
Well, my Christmas village needs 75,000 watts.
那还只是我的糖果棒直升机的用电呢
And that's just to work my candy cane helicopter.
苏菲最近忙于波兰同乡会圣诞装饰大赛
Sophie's been so busy with the Polish Society Decorating Contest.
我们都好几天没来一炮了
We haven't had sex in days.
我得打败我的宿敌  菲尔卡·波本斯基
Well, I got to beat my nemesis, Felka Bobenski.
每年都是她赢
She wins every year.
她就像是圣诞装饰界的《摩登家庭》
She's like the Modern Family of Christmas decorations
你知道谁今年圣诞节很忧郁[蓝]吗
You know who's having a blue Christmas this year?
我憋得铁青的蛋蛋
My balls.
我好喜欢这城市过节的时候
I love this city at the holidays.
对啊  流浪汉撒的尿都冻住了
Yeah, the urine's all frozen
所以你不太闻得到臭味
so you can't really smell it.
曼哈顿是最适合买好圣诞礼物的地方了
Manhattan is the best place to buy quality Christmas gifts.
我们有四十块钱
We have 40 bucks.
那些行李袋里
Now, where are those duffel bags
装满偷来的电器用品  然后只卖半价的
full of stolen electronics sold for half the price
肯尼亚难民呢
by Nairobi refugees?
我们最好赶紧找到他们
Well, we better find them soon
不然我要放弃  学去打折电器行的人们
or I'm going to give up and go to Radio Shack
也去打折电器行里买礼物了
like everyone else who goes to Radio Shack.
天啊  麦克斯
Oh my God, Max.
我童年的银行
My childhood bank.
你童年时期就有银行啦
You had a childhood bank?
我连童年都没有
I didn't even have a childhood.
来嘛  跟我进去  我几个月就会来一次
Come on, let's go. I stop in every few months
故意被保安摄像头拍到
to get caught on the security cameras,
好让人们觉得我还在这圈子里
so people will think I'm still in the mix.
故意被保安摄像头拍到吗
Trying to get caught on security cameras?
我们可真是两类人啊
Whoa, we are different.
我们就转一圈  不过既然都来了
Yeah, we'll just go in and while we're in here,
要不就问问商业贷款吧
well, I don't know, ask for a business loan.
我们不许借商业贷款
We are not getting a business loan!
你把我骗来市里
You tricked me into coming to the city.
好歹也有点人性  把我打晕后塞货车里送来
At least knock me out and put me in the trunk like a person.
行  懂你意思  不贷款
Okay, I hear you. No loan.
但好歹我们可以进去
But can we at least go in there
让我能闻到一下保险库的味道
so I can get a hit off some vault fumes
以及一杯免费的圣诞可可吧
and a complimentary Christmas cocoa?
好吧  我也想来一杯
Yeah, I want one too.
外面真是太冷
It's so cold out here
我的胸罩要告我硬起的奶头蓄意伤人了
my bra is suing my nipples for assault.
我说要不贷个1万5吧
I'd say we ask for $15,000.
我差点就要闻到百元大钞的味儿了
So close I almost smelled a 100.
你脑子有病啊
What is with you?
如果我想要你整天骗我
If I wanted you to keep lying to me,
我跟你恋爱就好啦
I'd date you.
麦克斯  我们需要更多资金
Max, we need more capital
才能大量的做我们的T恤
so we can buy our shirts in bulk,
然后如果我们更加努力
and then, if we work even harder,
我们的利润就能加倍呢
we can double our profit.
行  但是我们俩连信用核查都不会过
Okay, we won't pass even the credit check.
如果检查我的社保号码
According to my Social Security number,
会发现我好多年前就死于船只爆炸了
I died in a boat explosion years ago.
现在是申请的好时机
This is the time to apply.
银行家在圣诞节比较有愧疚感
Bankers have more guilt at Christmastime
因为《生活多美好》的关系
because of It's A Wonderful Life.
而且也因为他们都是犹太人
And also 'cause they're Jewish.
我才是有商业学位的人
I'm the one with the business degree,
这事你得相信我
and you have to trust me on this.
其实呢  你说得有道理
You know what? You're right.
你才是商业天才  我懂个屁啊
You're the business genius. What do I know?
咱们进去贷款吧
Let's go get that loan.
谢谢支持
Thank you!
我早该看出你这么配合是耍我的
Yeah, I should have known that was too good to be true.
麦克斯  别这样
Max, come on.
银行就在那里  我们的T恤就在这里
The bank's there. Our shirt's in here.
我们就进去  给人家看  然后申请贷款
Let's just go in, show them, and apply for that loan.
-好不好  -不好
- Please! - No.
-求你了  -不给
-拜托嘛  -不行
- Please! - No.
刚才这样就是名为
And that right there was a little something
"我们求人批贷款"的样子
called "us asking for a bank loan."
现在走吧
Now let's go.
你不告诉我真实的原因
I'm not leaving here until you tell me
我打死也不走
what the underlying issue is.
因为我已经不爱你了
I'm not in love with you anymore.
麦克斯  别闹了
Max, be serious.
这T恤是你的设计
This whole T-shirt was your idea.
你到底有啥问题
What's the real problem?
问题就是这个
That's the problem.
这设计是我想出来的
Those shirts were my idea
我做出来的东西不可能价值1万5
and nothing that comes from me is worth $15,000.
麦克斯  这些T恤绝对是赚钱机器
Max, I know these T-shirts are a money-maker.
我是有"赚钱机器"啊  不过不是那衣服
Oh, I have a money-maker and that's not it.
我能证明给你看
I can prove it.
这间精品店叫罗德尼
Look, this is Rodney,
我是小时候会来买的抢钱服饰店
my childhood over-priced clothing store.
如果来之前我知道今天是童年回顾之旅
If I had known we were going on the childhood tour today,
我会穿上更舒服的鞋子
I would have worn more comfortable shoes
然后宅在家里
and stayed home.
你看到假人身上的衣服了吗
See the shirt on the mannequin?
起码要两百块
At least $200.
我们这件衣服没理由不能卖一样价钱
And there's no reason we can't sell ours for just as much.
我带你看  跟上[关注我]
I'll show you. Follow me.
跟你进来可以  但关注你的照片分享网不行
Oh, okay, I will. But not on Instagram,
因为你是刷屏狂魔
'cause you're out of control.
这地方真高大上
This place is fancy
连我这去过纽瓦克港务局的人都赞叹呢
and I've been to the new Port Authority in Newark.
信我就对了
Just trust me, okay?
赶紧把这王大仁的高跟鞋买了
You need to jump on those Wang pumps
不然它们会像本·阿弗莱克的《消失的爱人》
or like Ben Affleck, they will be "Gone, girl."
我来负责谈  我会说他那套语言
Let me do the talking. I speak his language.
那是什么语言  基佬语[葡萄牙]吗
And what language is that? Portu-gays?
姑娘们好  欢迎光临罗德尼
Hello, ladies. Welcome to Rodney.
我叫巴里
I'm Barry.
你们是来节日购物的吗
Doing a little holiday shopping?
为防信仰人种不同  我们不能说圣诞快乐
We're not allowed to say Christmas.
其实我们是来做节日"卖"物
As a matter of fact, we're doing a little holiday selling.
你们是来"卖货"的吗
Oh, you're "selling."
懂了  摇头丸还是古柯碱
Got it. Molly? Coke?
我没兴趣买
Not that I'm interested.
我2010年的火岛同性恋节后就戒了
I've been clean since Fire Island 2010.
还有2012年那次之后
And 2012.
人生很难吧  又"基"歪又没药嗑
It must be hard to not be high and be you.
因为像我这样
Because it's hard for me
要接近你又没药嗑已经很辛苦了
to just be near you and not be high.
是啊  你懂啊  姑娘
Yeah, you get it, girl.
其实我们想看看你是否有兴趣
Actually, we wanted to see if you'd be interested
卖我们其中一件有趣图案T恤
in selling one of our fabulous graphic t-shirts.
不不不不不不不
Oh, n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n--
确定一定以及肯定不行
all sorts of "no", Okay?
虽然我很喜欢毡帽  阿拉伯衣  跟小男孩
As much as I love a fez, a caftan, and a teenage boy,
但这里又不是摩洛哥
this isn't Morocco.
你这个不行还真是又臭又长啊
That's a really long and boring version of "No."
感觉你刚才演了一出"不行  一个女人的独白"
It's like you just did  "No! The One Woman Show."
这是我们的T恤
Here's our T-shirt--
听好了
Look.
就如我会对年轻版马克·雅克布说的话
I'll tell you two what I said to a young Marc Jacobs.
别死缠着不放  "不要"就是不要
Stop offering, I'm off the junk.
节日快乐
Merry Holiday.
我来给小乐儿看看啥叫过节
I'll show Mary a holiday.
我们的衣服跟这些一样好
Our shirts are just as good as these.
他只是需要亲眼看到
He just needs to see it.
给  帮我拿着
Here, hold this.
你谁啊  《美国精神病人》吗
What are you? American Psycho?
有人一对你说"不行
As soon as someone says "No" to you,
你就开始把女人大卸八块
you start dismembering women.
我扒不掉她的衣服
I can't get her shirt off.
告诉她你准她"做"完留下过夜
Tell her she can spend the night
明早你会买松饼给她吃
and you'll buy her a waffle in the morning.
把我们的衣服给我
Okay, hand me our shirt.
不是吧
Seriously?
真的假的
你  们  闹  呢
Ser-I-ous-ly?
真好看
So cute.
看后面的字样"奶油[精液]满满"
And look on the back, "Cream Filled."
搞笑
Funny.
大家会觉得我有个性
People will think I have a personality.
巴里  帮我跟其他东西包一起
Barry, put this with my other stuff.
多少钱
How much?
别信他说他戒了  绝对是嗨高了
Forget the sober story. That guy is high.
我买十件
I'll take ten.
犹太光明节时送这衣服给我那些
They'll make great Hanukkah gifts
不讨厌自己手臂的朋友  应该挺不错
for my friends who don't hate their arms.
我们全部衣服被一个有钱心死的女人承包了
All our shirts just got bought by a rich dead lady.
周五再送30件来
I'll need 30 more by Friday.
是的  我一直在等呢
Yes, I'm still holding.
我需要下订单加急制作一批T恤
I need to place a rush t-shirt order.
别别别  别再帮我转接客服部了
No, no, no, no, no. Don't put me on hold again.
我已经听了七遍圣诞神曲
I've been through seven rounds of
《奶奶被驯鹿撞死了》
Grandma Got Run Over By A Reindeer.
现在她又被撞第八遍了
And she just got run over again.
既然现在有那个疯子基佬给的T恤钱
Now that we have all this crazy gay t-shirt money,
我想我们可以花大钱买豪礼啦
I think we should up the prices on these gifts.
就这么定了  我们送厄尔一辆车
So we agree, we're getting Earl a car.
送苏菲一栋她梦寐以求的湖边别墅
Sophie is getting the country house with the lake she's always wanted.
麦克斯  虽然我们的T恤在店里售价是300美元
Max, Rodney is selling our shirts for 300,
但我们每件只能拿到25美元
but we only get 25 of that.
而且750美元哪够买房子啊
And you can't buy a house for $750.
你以为是底特律啊
It's not Detroit.
是的  你好你好  终于接通了
Yes, hi, hi, hi. Finally a person.
我需要订购50件T恤  周五前送货
I need 50 T-shirts by Friday.
但你们的名片上写着"保证第二天送货"啊
But your business card says you guarantee next-day delivery.
你不能保证名片上的"保证"吗
Oh, you can't "Guarantee" that guarantee?
该到奥列格了
Okay, now Oleg.
你说送他什么好呢  这个男人啥都没有
What do you get a man who has nothing,
但又总是啥都给你看
but shows you everything?
你哪来的脸说"还有什么我可以帮你的吗"
What do you mean "Is there anything else you can help me with?"
你什么时候帮到我过
when did you help me at all?
我在想如果"奶奶"是你的员工
And I'm beginning to think if Grandma works for you,
她肯定不是被驯鹿撞死的
she didn't get run over by that reindeer,
她一定卧雪橇自杀的
she threw herself under a sleigh.
那好  送苏菲一瓶果汁
So, Sophie's getting a Snapple.
跟去年的礼物一样
Like last year.
麦克斯  我们不能放弃  我们自己也可以做
Max, we can't give up. We can do them ourselves.
我们只需要找别人来做就行
We just need someone else to do them.
姑娘们  快出来接客
Come on, let's go.
外面的客人从罗宾·西克
There are customers who have been here
还算回事的时候就在了
since Robin Thicke was relevant.
等等  阿憨  你丝印制作了那些漂亮的卡片
Wait a minute, Han. You silk-screened all those beautiful cards.
你也有艺术方面的天分啊
You have an artistic side.
是啊  但没有后面[屁股]
Yeah, but no backside.
而"前面"根本不能掏出外面见人
And a front side that shouldn't be allowed outside.
为什么要这么久啊
Why is this taking so long?
那些圣诞卡都是你一个人做
You did all those Christmas cards.
小生物干起活来不都飞快的吗
Aren't small creatures supposed to be fast?
老实说  那些卡片本应该是去年的圣诞礼物
Truth be told, those were supposed to be ready last year.
但急什么呢
But, what was the rush?
你们俩肯定会死赖着不走
You two weren't going anywhere.
阿憨  你只需回答我"是"或"不是"
Han, just a simple "Yes" or "No".
我不会怪你的
No judgment.
你是不是跟这台机器发生关系了
Have you had sex with this machine?
唯一比你俩为我干活还惨的事
The only thing worse than you two working for me
就是我为你俩干活
is me working for you.
连水都不给人家喝
You haven't even given me water.
水是给完工的人准备的
Water is for closers.
"完工的人"是指真正完成衣服的人
By "closers," I mean people who actually make clothes.
会是谁呀
Who's that?
阿憨  你是不是向儿童保护机构揭发我们了
Han, did you call Child Protective Service on us?
你身上的淤青也可以是别人弄的啊
'Cause those bruises could be from anyone.
阿憨  你两个小时才做出一件T恤
Han, you've only made one shirt in two hours.
神作啊  你是想要1部神作电影《公民凯恩》
And it's a masterpiece. Do you want one Citizen Kane
还是30部粗制滥造的《好景在望》
or 30 Here Comes the Booms?
伙计们  我需要你们帮忙
Guys, I need your help.
苏菲马上就到  她需要一些鼓励
Sophie's right behind me and needs some cheering up.
她昨晚惊醒
I haven't seen her this depressed
发现在"被做爱"后  她是第一次这么低落
since she woke up mid-coitus last night.
大家好
Hi.
你们好  姑娘们
Hi. Hi, girls.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
问一句
Quick question:
如果打开炉灶  关上所有窗
if I were to turn on that oven and close all the windows,
我会死吗
would I die?
不会
Nope.
否则我就不会在这里
Otherwise I wouldn't be standing here
站在"金正-一日一件"旁边
next to Kim Jong-Only-Done-One.
苏菲  发生什么事了
Sophie, what's the problem?
你可以在阿憨干活时告诉他
Tell Han while he gets back to work.
还有阿憨  动作快点
And Han, pick up the pace
不然我又要开始掐你了
or I'm going to start the pinching again.
我要输掉这次圣诞装饰大赛了
I'm gonna lose the Christmas decorating contest.
我活着还有什么意义呢
Oh, I have nothing to live for.
卡洛琳  你大概每天都在想这个问题吧
Oh, Caroline, this is probably how you feel every day.
苏菲的对手在她房子前
Sophie's competition made a live-action
做了一个实景圣诞礼物工厂
North Pole workshop in front of her house.
而我只有发光的耶稣诞生图
Well, all I got upstairs is a light-up nativity
还有从百货花2万5千美元买的圣诞装饰物
and $25,000 worth of Target Christmas decorations.
她昨晚烧坏[吹]了五根保险丝
She blew five fuses last night.
我从未想过我会嫉妒一根小小的保险丝
I never thought I'd be jealous of a fuse.
苏菲  我们现在真的没空帮你
Sophie, we really can't get into this now.
T恤的进度远远落后
We are way behind with these T-shirts.
而这批T恤是我们百年难得一遇的机会
And these T-shirts are a once in a lifetime chance
能帮我们打开一扇新的生意大门呢
for us to go to a new place with our business.
我明白  姑娘们
Oh yeah, I hear you, girls.
我是说  我干嘛坐在这
I mean, what am I doing here
为某个白痴比赛忧心忡忡
sitting worrying about some silly contest?
这可是圣诞节啊
It's Christmas.
来吧  各位
Come on everybody.
我们应该一起帮她们
We should all be helping the girls.
真的吗  那真是太棒了
Really? That would be so amazing.
当然  你甚至不用报答我
Sure! And you wouldn't even have to pay me back
真的不用明晚借出你们的马厩和马
by letting me use your barn and your horse tomorrow night
更不用集体参与  帮我创造一个耶稣诞生实景
for a live nativity scene, which you would all have to be in.
或类似的场景
Or something like that.
我们好像被节日版花式拐骗了
I think we just had a seasonal shake-down.
阿憨在做最后一件了  我们马上就要完成了
Han's doing the last one. We're gonna make it.
真不敢相信你挂着那胡子  还能这么高兴
I can't believe you're in such a good mood with that beard.
上周你发现下巴长了两根毛时
Last week when you found those two chin hairs,
可没这么开心
you weren't so chipper.
我只是开心我终于有新衣服穿了
I'm just so happy I have new clothes.
最后一件T恤了
Okay, final shirt.
然后你们俩就可以不用来烦我这个小天使了
Then I get you two out of my angel hair.
阿憨  如果没有你
Han, you know, if it weren't for you,
我们俩绝对不可能完成
we would have never gotten this done.
你真是一个小天使啊
You really are a little angel.
是啊  但我还是真惊讶
Yeah, you are. But I'm still surprised
苏菲居然没让你扮婴儿耶稣
you weren't cast as the baby.
她问过我  但我拒绝了
Oh, I was asked, but I declined.
我花了十年时间才摆脱尿布
I spent ten year getting out of diapers.
我可不想穿回去
I'm not getting back in.
阿憨  作为你的圣诞礼物
Han, for your Christmas gift,
我就当没听见这句话吧
I'll pretend I never heard that.
各就各位
Places everybody.
裁判要来了  我准备好了
The judges are coming. I'm ready.
约瑟夫好了  椰菜娃娃版耶稣也准备好了
Joseph's ready. Cabbage Patch Christ is ready.
快来吧
Come on!
她露乳沟算怎么回事啊
What's with the cleavage?
就是
I know.
她是淫母玛利亚吧
She's like the Not-So-Virgin Mary.
天使  牧羊人  长胡子的女人
Angel, Shepherd, Lady with the beard,
快点  在马厩集合
come on, get in the stable.
马厩[稳定]
Stable?
我们看起来像一群精神"不稳定"的人吧
The way we look it should be an "Unstable."
大家准备好了吗  我要去开门了
Everybody ready? I'm going to open the barn door.
我想你下面那个"门"已经开了一条缝了
Yeah, I think your barn door's already a little open.
再问一遍  我扮谁啊
Okay now, who am I again?
圣战士吗
Voltron?
我不骗你们  有一位博士
I'm not gonna lie. One of the wise men
可能抽了一点"没药大麻"
might have smoked some "Myrrh-ijuana."
这圣诞礼物相当不错  麦克斯
That was a very nice Christmas gift, Max.
多谢夸奖  厄尔  对了苏菲
Thanks, Earl. By the way, Sophie,
马厩以及我们穿成一群白痴
the barn and us dressed like idiots?
那是你的圣诞礼物
That's your Christmas gift.
对了  晚点要跟奥列格上床哦
Oh, and hey, bang Oleg later.
奥列格  这是你的圣诞礼物
Oleg, that's your gift.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
在裁判来之前  让我们环顾四周
Before they come in, let's just take a moment to look around
好好领会一下圣诞节的真正精神
and really let in the true spirit of Christmas.
我不记得有给你写独白啊
I don't remember writing you a monologue.
把嘴闭上
Shut up!
快滚去马那边站着
Get your ass over by the horse.
阿憨  快放音乐
Come on, Han. Hit the music.
好了  各位
All right, everybody,
要一脸圣洁哦
look holy.
我最多只能让我的内裤这样
Best I can do is my underwear.
我靠
Oh , crap!
没错  菲尔卡
Oh, that's right, Felka.
老娘就是上帝他妈
I'm the freakin' mother of God.
我们赢了
We won!
真高兴我们赢了
I'm so happy we won.
我们赢了  我们赢了
We won! We Won!
好了  表演结束
Okay, show's over.
把娃娃扔掉  我上楼等你
Dump the kid, I'll be upstairs.
麦克斯  帮我照顾椰菜娃娃耶稣
Max, take care of Cabbage Patch Christ.
给  阿憨  你有一个一样大小的伙伴了
Here, Han. You got a buddy your own size.
非常感谢  巴里
Thank you so much, Barry.
记住  我还要多订50件T恤
And remember, I want 50 more shirts
新年的第一天  我从戒毒所回来要看到
after the first of the year when I'm back from rehab.
因为姑娘们  我圣诞节准备要大爽特爽啦
'Cause ladies, I am planning a very white Christmas.
麦克斯  这太棒了
Max, this is amazing!
你知道刚才在里面发生了什么事吗
Do you know what just happened in there?
知道啊  我偷了一副超酷无指手套
Yeah, I stole some dope-ass fingerless gloves.
他们现在可是我们的生意伙伴
We're in business with them now.
你得把手套还回去
You have to bring those back.
我是偷给你
I got them for you.
好吧
Okay.
这就像一个圣诞奇迹
This is like a Christmas miracle.
我们的T恤在曼哈顿
Our shirts are being sold in
最高档傲慢的精品店中出售
the most exclusive bitchy boutique in Manhattan
而且他们还想下订单  要更多T恤
and they want more, lots more.
我们去你的童年银行吧
Hey, let's go into your childhood bank.
我得尿一泡成人尿
I need to take an adult pee.
好的  但这里不是咱家  所以记住
Okay, but this isn't home, so remember,
尿完之后记得把马桶座放下
put the seat down when you're done.
我们进去之后  还可以申请带贷款啊
And while we're in there, we can apply for that loan.
不不不  不行
No, no, no, no, no. We can't.
现在轮到我害怕了
Now I'm afraid.
干嘛  问题到底是什么
Come on, what's the real issue here?
我们刚刚大获成功
We just had this amazing success.
感觉我们终于时来运转
And it looks like things are going our way,
但如果进去  有可能会被人当头棒喝
and if we go in there, it could all be ruined.
你知道什么事更能毁掉我们一生吗
You know what would ruin our lives even more?
就是我们不去贷款  而是盯着阿憨
If we don't get that loan and have to spend hours
在我们魔掌下  花无数小时为我们完成T恤
with Han standing under us trying to finish those shirts.
这就是真的《圣诞夜惊魂》[电影]了
Well, that's a real "Nightmare Before Christmas."
进去吧
Let's go.
很好  因为我已经滴几滴出来了
Good, cause I'm starting to pee a little.
他贷给我们了
He gave us a loan!
在这条街上工作的人都嗑嗨了吗
Is everyone who works on the street high?
我真不敢相信  完全没出事
I can't believe it. It didn't go bad.
我想要的一切都到手了
I'm getting everything I want.
你走人行道外侧吧
Walk on the outside of the sidewalk.
我要被公车撞了
I'm gonna get hit by a bus.
他怎么会批贷款给我们啊
I mean, how could he give us a loan?
我都没露咪咪给他看就批了
I didn't even have to flash my boobs.
那为什么你还是露了
Then why did you do it?
不知道  他钱都撒出来了
I don't know. They were making it rain.
我不露不舒服啊
I felt obliged.
麦克斯  你有一块钱吗
Max, do you have a dollar?
不知道啊  你有钱找开我的一万块吗
I don't know. Do you have change for 10,000?
有啊  干嘛用
Yeah, here. For what?
给没我们幸运的人们
For those less fortunate
安妮·海瑟薇在这里吗
Anne Hathaway's here?
天啊  你看  你看
Oh, my God. Look! Look!
不是吧  不是吧
Whoa, no way! No way!
麦克斯  我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
Max, I have chills.
毕竟下着雪你露出手指  冷到起鸡皮很正常
Well, it is snowing and there's no fingers on those gloves.
我好喜欢这手套
I love these.
抱歉我什么都没给你
I'm sorry I didn't get you anything.
但我真的不是小偷
I'm just not a thief.
谁说你什么都没有给我
What do you mean you didn't get me anything?
你给了我一切  你看
You got me everything. Look.